[{"answer": "Yeah. What's his name", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend what", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Uh... my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah. I just wish he has a different name", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You can't ask a person to change their name", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend the masseuse", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No! How many times do I have to go out with her before I get a massage", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You know it's like you never see a really attractive woman getting a traffic ticket", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well I've never met your sister but obviously these are not har", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Now you however, you, I like.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What do you think I'm doing?   ", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yea", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You were", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You were", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I didn't pick up anything", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "The second time I sent the noodle back, I tought she made a face..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I tought I saw a face", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No. The sex was fabulous", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What were her exac", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "U", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "\"I don't like him", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Not everybody likes everybody", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Not everybody likes everybody", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You were very nice", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "And then the gam", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh I got the ball", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Of course", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What, do you think I've never had a massage before", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No, I don't know. Maybe you haven't. You know, not everybody's seen a massage table", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Anyway, I don't even get a thank you. I don't get it", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What, do you think I've never had a massage before", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend, frankly, I'm getting a little tired of hearing about her", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Nonsense. This one's fine.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Go? Why go anywhere?  Ahh, that feels good. Yeah. That's, uh... That's good.  Yeah, that's nice. That's very nice", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "All right my friend. I have had just about enough of this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I am talking about you and my friend. You're completely obsessed with her", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Masseuse.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "*Yo", "qsentId": 40}]